{
    "title": "Basketball",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Yao Ming was the number one draft pick in the 2002 draft. Who went second overall?",
            "choices": [
                "Robert Archibald",
                "Vincent Yarbrough",
                "Carlos Boozer",
                "Jay Williams"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Before becoming the Houston Rockets, where did the team play?",
            "choices": [
                "San Diego",
                "Fort Wayne",
                "St. Paul",
                "Cleveland"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the Coach of the Year in the 1967-68 season for his efforts with the Hawks?",
            "choices": [
                "Dolph Shayes",
                "Gene Shue",
                "Bill Fitch",
                "Richie Guerin"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "The NBA MVP Award first began for the 1955-56 season. Who won this inaugural award?",
            "choices": [
                "Dave Bing",
                "Earl Monroe",
                "Hal Greer",
                "Bob Pettit"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Sidney Wicks played for 10 seasons with Portland, Boston, and San Diego. In his first six seasons, Wicks' averaged over 20 points per game. Which college did he attend?",
            "choices": [
                "Grambling",
                "Auburn",
                "UCLA",
                "Georgetown"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Which NBA player scored the most points in all the 1990s?",
            "choices": [
                "Scottie Pippen",
                "Karl Malone",
                "Shawn Kemp",
                "Charles Barkley"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following rookies of the year, won the award as a Laker?",
            "choices": [
                "Kareem Abdul Jabbar",
                "Jamaal Wilkes",
                "Wilt Chamberlain",
                "Elgin Baylor"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following retired with a career scoring average of over 30 points per game?",
            "choices": [
                "Wilt Chamberlain",
                "Dominique Wilkins",
                "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
                "Larry Bird"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I was born in Melbourne, Australia. I was schooled at Scotch College in Perth. After playing for New Mexico, I was the Timberwolves' first pick in the 1991 draft. I retired after playing in 10 NBA seasons with Minnesota, Chicago, Phoenix, and New York. Who am I?",
            "choices": [
                "Toni Kukoc",
                "Chris Padtke",
                "Mick Gaelin",
                "Luc Longley"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "So much talk about Wilt Chamberlain scoring 100 points in a game on March 2, 1962. Who did his Philadelphia Warriors defeat in that game, 169-147?",
            "choices": [
                "New York Knicks",
                "San Diego Clippers",
                "Baltimore Bullets",
                "Boston Celtics"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        }
    ]
}